[
  {
    "question": "qa.whatIsGooglementor",
    "answer": "qa.whatIsGooglementorAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.whatAreLists",
    "answer": "qa.whatAreListsAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.howToUseList",
    "answer": "qa.howToUseListAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.areListsFree",
    "answer": "qa.areListsFreeAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.howToHideList",
    "answer": "qa.howToHideListAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.howToShowList",
    "answer": "qa.howToShowListAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.howOftenUpdated",
    "answer": "qa.howOftenUpdatedAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.whyTravelInsurance",
    "answer": "qa.whyTravelInsuranceAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.whoCanBenefit",
    "answer": "qa.whoCanBenefitAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.whyBuyEsim",
    "answer": "qa.whyBuyEsimAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.whyAiraloEsim",
    "answer": "qa.whyAiraloEsimAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.howToContact",
    "answer": "qa.howToContactAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.areListsSecure",
    "answer": "qa.areListsSecureAnswer"
  },
  {
    "question": "qa.canDeleteList",
    "answer": "qa.canDeleteListAnswer"
  }
]
